<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Horus Heresy]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Horus Heresy</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:21:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:21:45 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Evelyn]]></title><link>pc&apos;s/humans/evelyn.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PC&apos;s/Humans/Evelyn.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:32:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Call To Arms!]]></title><description><![CDATA[From: <a data-href="Grand Marshall Name Coming Soon" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Grand Marshall Name Coming Soon</a>
Subject: Open Contract<br>King <a data-href="ToBeNamed" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">ToBeNamed</a> of <a data-href="Region" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Region</a> has passed away unexpectedly at the age of 28. His heir <a data-href="PrinceKid" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PrinceKid</a> is only 6 years old, so advisors and nobles have formed a council to take care of the kingdom until he is of age to take over. However, in the chaos following the unexpected death several insurgent groups have arisen. Normally they would be handled by the local police and militia, however they appear to have acquired a cache of HORUS tech and are proving elusive. In this time of turmoil, we humbly request the aid of any willing to take up arms to restore peace in these troubled times.]]></description><link>inbox/call-to-arms!.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Inbox/Call To Arms!.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:52:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Veda Sulati]]></title><link>pc&apos;s/humans/veda-sulati.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PC&apos;s/Humans/Veda Sulati.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:43:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cooper Ellys]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-href="Duelist#Tier 2" href="references/talents/duelist.html#Tier 2" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="" data-link-path="References/Talents/Duelist.md">Duelist &gt; Tier 2</a>, <a data-href="Skirmisher#Tier 2" href="references/talents/skirmisher.html#Tier 2" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="" data-link-path="References/Talents/Skirmisher.md">Skirmisher &gt; Tier 2</a>, <a data-href="Combined Arms#Tier 1" href="references/talents/combined-arms.html#Tier 1" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="" data-link-path="References/Talents/Combined Arms.md">Combined Arms &gt; Tier 1</a>, <a data-href="Leader#Tier 1" href="references/talents/leader.html#Tier 1" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="" data-link-path="References/Talents/Leader.md">Leader &gt; Tier 1</a>]]></description><link>pc&apos;s/humans/cooper-ellys.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PC&apos;s/Humans/Cooper Ellys.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:42:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Maya]]></title><description><![CDATA[Metastatic Paralysis
When an attack roll against the Gorgon lands on 1–2, it automatically misses and the attacker becomes Stunned until the end of their next turn.
Gaze
The Gorgon can take two reactions per turn, instead of one.
Guardian
Adjacent allied characters may use the Gorgon for hard cover.
]]></description><link>pc&apos;s/mechs/maya.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PC&apos;s/Mechs/Maya.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Raiju]]></title><link>pc&apos;s/nhp&apos;s/raiju.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PC&apos;s/NHP&apos;s/Raiju.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:54:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Company Roster]]></title><link>pc&apos;s/company-roster.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PC&apos;s/Company Roster.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fold Knife]]></title><link>references/gear/fold-knife.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Gear/Fold Knife.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dream]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hunter
1/round, the Mourning Cloak may deal +1d6 bonus damage on hit with a melee attack if its target has no adjacent characters, or if the Mourning Cloak is the only character adjacent to the target.
Biotic Components
The Mourning Cloak gains +1 accuracy on Agility checks and saves.
Blinkspace Jump Teleport to a space within range 3d6. You don’t require line of sight, but attempts to teleport to occupied spaces cause you to remain stationary and lose this action. If you roll the same number on all three dice, you disappear until your group rests, at which point you reappear nearby. Stabilize Singularity
For the rest of the scene, you teleport when you Boost or make a standard move.
<a data-href="Overpower Caliber" href="references/core-bonus/overpower-caliber.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="" data-link-path="References/Core Bonus/Overpower Caliber.md">Overpower Caliber</a><br><a data-href="Variable Sword" href="references/gear/variable-sword.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="#accurate" data-link-path="References/Gear/Variable Sword.md">Variable Sword</a><br><a data-href="Variable Sword" href="references/gear/variable-sword.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="#accurate" data-link-path="References/Gear/Variable Sword.md">Variable Sword</a> / <a data-href="Fold Knife" href="references/gear/fold-knife.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="#accurate" data-link-path="References/Gear/Fold Knife.md">Fold Knife</a> // <a data-href="Overpower Caliber" href="references/core-bonus/overpower-caliber.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="" data-link-path="References/Core Bonus/Overpower Caliber.md">Overpower Caliber</a><br><a data-href="Fade Cloak" href="references/systems/fade-cloak.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="#unique #quick-action" data-link-path="References/Systems/Fade Cloak.md">Fade Cloak</a>, <a data-href="Hunter Logic Suite" href="references/systems/hunter-logic-suite.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="#invade #unique" data-link-path="References/Systems/Hunter Logic Suite.md">Hunter Logic Suite</a>, <a data-href="Singularity Motivator" href="references/systems/singularity-motivator.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="#unique #reaction" data-link-path="References/Systems/Singularity Motivator.md">Singularity Motivator</a>, <a data-href="Type-3 Projected Shield" href="references/systems/type-3-projected-shield.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-link-tags="#heat-self #protocol #shield #unique" data-link-path="References/Systems/Type-3 Projected Shield.md">Type-3 Projected Shield</a>]]></description><link>pc&apos;s/mechs/dream.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PC&apos;s/Mechs/Dream.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Raiju (Mech)]]></title><description><![CDATA[¿%:?EXTR!UDE GUN
GUN: GUN
By the way, I know everything
When it would roll damage, the Pegasus can instead deal the average damage based on the number of dice rolled, as follows: 1d3 (2), 1d6 (4), 2d6 (7), 3d6 (11), 4d6 (14). This must be decided before rolling damage.
[ERROR] [range 15][1 AP Kinetic Damage] Your mech’s omnigun is a piece of experimental hardware so advanced that it defies physics: it doesn’t require a mount, nor does it have a weapon type or size – meaning that it can’t be modified or benefit from your talents. You can’t attack normally with this weapon. Instead, 1/round, as a free action during your turn, you can use it to deal 1 AP kinetic damage to a character within Range 15 and line of sight. This doesn’t count as an attack, hits automatically, ignores cover, bypasses Immunity, and its damage can’t be reduced or ignored in any way. No rule in this book or any other supersedes this. Fire Omnigun 1/round, as a free action during your turn, deal 1 AP kinetic damage to a character within Range 15 and line of sight. This doesn’t count as an attack, hits automatically, ignores cover, bypasses Immunity, and its damage can’t be reduced or ignored in any way. No rule supersedes this.
For the rest of this scene, you can use the Ushabti Omnigun 3/round, instead of 1/round.
]]></description><link>pc&apos;s/mechs/raiju-(mech).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PC&apos;s/Mechs/Raiju (Mech).md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 05:42:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Type-3 Projected Shield]]></title><description><![CDATA[ Project Shield Nominate a character within line of sight: all ranged or melee attacks that they make against you or that you make against them gain +2 Difficulty until the start of your next turn.
]]></description><link>references/systems/type-3-projected-shield.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Systems/Type-3 Projected Shield.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Singularity Motivator]]></title><description><![CDATA[ Exposed Singularity 1/Round Your mech takes damage You may immediately teleport to a free space within 1d6 spaces
]]></description><link>references/systems/singularity-motivator.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Systems/Singularity Motivator.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hunter Logic Suite]]></title><description><![CDATA[ Stalk Prey You infect the target with a viral logic that wipes your image from their sensors. They treat you as Invisible until you next take damage from them. This can only affect one target at a time. Terrify You infect the target with a viral logic that makes your mech appear horrifying. Until the end of their next turn, they become Impaired and cannot make any voluntary movements that bring them closer to you.
]]></description><link>references/systems/hunter-logic-suite.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Systems/Hunter Logic Suite.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:22:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fade Cloak]]></title><description><![CDATA[Activate Fade Cloak When activated, you immediately move out of phase with realspace, becoming intangible. While intangible, you may move through obstructions, but not end your turn within them. You cannot interact with any other object or character or be interacted with in any way (e.g., taking or dealing damage).
Roll 1d6 at the start of each of your turns: on 3 or less, you return to realspace until the start of your next turn; on 4+, you remain intangible.
This system remains active for the rest of the scene, or until you deactivate it as a quick action.
]]></description><link>references/systems/fade-cloak.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Systems/Fade Cloak.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:14:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Overpower Caliber]]></title><description><![CDATA[Choose one weapon. 1/round, when you hit with an attack, you can cause it to deal +1d6 bonus damage.]]></description><link>references/core-bonus/overpower-caliber.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Core Bonus/Overpower Caliber.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:46:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Leader]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gain 3 Leadership Dice, which are d6s, and gain the Issue Order Free Action.
You can’t use Leadership Dice from other characters as long as you have any remaining. If you have none, you regain 1 Leadership Die when you rest or regain all when you perform a Full Repair.
Leadership dice are consumed when expended. Issue Order 1/turn, on your turn as a free action, you may issue an order to an allied PC you can communicate with, describing a course of action, and give them a Leadership Die. They may either expend the Leadership Die to gain +1 Accuracy on any action that directly follows from that order, or they may return it to you as a free action. Allies can have one Leadership Die at a time, which lasts until used or until the end of the current scene.
Gain 5 Leadership Dice instead of 3; additionally, you can now issue a command as a reaction at the start of any other player’s turn, any number of times per round. Issue Command Another player starts their turn. You may issue a command to an allied PC you can communicate with, describing a course of action, and give them a Leadership Die. They may either expend the Leadership Die to gain +1 Accuracy on any action that directly follows from that order, or they may return it to you as a free action. Allies can have one Leadership Die at a time, which lasts until used or until the end of the current scene.
Gain 6 Leadership Dice instead of 5. Allies that have your Leadership Dice can expend them to reduce damage by –1d6 when taking damage or to deal +1d6 bonus damage when they hit with an attack.]]></description><link>references/talents/leader.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Talents/Leader.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:44:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Combined Arms]]></title><description><![CDATA[As long as you’re Engaged, you and any allies adjacent to you count as having soft cover.You don’t gain Difficulty from being Engaged.Whenever you hit a character with a melee attack, you gain +1 Accuracy on your next ranged attack against them; and, whenever you hit a character with a ranged attack, you gain +1 Accuracy on your next melee attack against them. This effect doesn’t stack.]]></description><link>references/talents/combined-arms.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Talents/Combined Arms.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 02:34:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Duelist]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gain +1 Accuracy on the first melee attack you make with a Main Melee weapon on your turn.1/round, when you hit with a Main Melee weapon, you gain 1 Blademaster Die – a d6 – up to a maximum of 3 Blademaster Die. They last until expended or the current scene ends. You can expend Blademaster Dice 1-for-1 for the following:
Parry: As a reaction when you’re hit by a melee attack, you gain Resistance to all damage, heat, and burn dealt by the attack.
Deflect: As a reaction when you’re hit by a ranged attack, you may roll any number of Blademaster Dice, expending them: if you roll a 5+ on any of these dice, you gain Resistance to all damage, heat, and burn dealt by the attack.
Feint: As a free action, choose an adjacent character: when moving, you ignore engagement and don’t provoke reactions from your target until the start of your next turn.
Trip: As a quick action, choose an adjacent character: they must pass an Agility save or fall Prone. Whatever the result, you may freely pass through their space until the end of your current turn, although you can’t end your turn in their space.
1/round, when you hit with a melee attack on your turn, you may spend a Blademaster Die to immediately Grapple or Ram your target as a free action after the attack has been resolved.]]></description><link>references/talents/duelist.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Talents/Duelist.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:43:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hunter]]></title><description><![CDATA[1/round, when you attack with an Auxiliary melee weapon, you may fly up to 3 spaces directly towards the targeted character before the attack. This movement ignores engagement and doesn’t provoke reactions.All your Auxiliary melee weapons gain Thrown 5, if they don’t have this property already – if they already have Thrown, it increases to Thrown 5. At the end of your turn, all weapons you have thrown this turn automatically return to you.1/round, when you hit a character with a melee attack, you may also throw an Auxiliary melee weapon as an attack against any character within Range as a free action. This attack can’t deal bonus damage.]]></description><link>references/talents/hunter.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Talents/Hunter.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skirmisher]]></title><description><![CDATA[At the start of your turn, you gain soft cover. You lose this cover if you attack or force another character to make a save.Before or after you Skirmish (including as a reaction, e.g. from Overwatch), you may move 2 spaces. This movement ignores engagement and doesn’t provoke reactions.The first attack taken as a reaction against you in any round automatically misses.]]></description><link>references/talents/skirmisher.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Talents/Skirmisher.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:43:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Variable Sword]]></title><link>references/gear/variable-sword.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">References/Gear/Variable Sword.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:32:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>